Guide to the photograph album Aviation in Mesopotamia Campaign WWI AD.MC.047
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- From the top left clockwise: the Bombay (Mumbai) harbor, two men at a submarine gun, a view of a ship, and a view of the same ship with a seaplane, possibly a Short 184, 8043., 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref22; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ports; Boats/Ships; Water; Transportation; English Writing; Men; Group Portraits; Buildings; Guns; Weapons; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Military/Soldiers; Navy; Air Force; Airplanes; Mumbai/Bombay, India
- Three portraits of men overhauling Sunbeam engines from Short 184 biplanes in the interior of workshop barge Vulcan., 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref23; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Navy; Air Force; Machines; Individual Portraits; Airplanes; Transportation; Iraq
- From the top left clockwise: the Royal Navy Air Service (RNAS) personnel aboard a transport ship, beds on the roof of Royal Navy Air Service (RNAS) headquarters, a view of a ship in Kut-el-Amara, and lightning during a storm in Basra., 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref24; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Boats/Ships; Crowds; Transportation; Navy; Air Force; Military/Soldiers; Men; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Amarah (Al-'Amāra), Iraq; Basra, Iraq; Buildings; Palm Trees; Architecture; Rivers; Water
- From the top left clockwise: a group of ferry boats in front of a Royal Flying Corps (RFC) barge, a street described as "Asha" near Basra, Royal Navy Air Service (RNAS) Insect- and Fly-class gunboats at Kut-el-Amara, and an RNAS camp at Orah., 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref25; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Palm Trees; Buildings; Architecture; Canals; Carriages/Coaches; Streets/Roads; Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Crowds; Amarah (Al-'Amāra), Iraq; Tents; Basra, Iraq; Military/Soldiers; Navy; Air Force
- From the top left clockwise: the Ctesiphon Arch (Taq Kasra), a crowd in a city, women carrying copper water pots in front of a mosque in Kut-el-Amara, and a view of settlement., 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref26; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Ctesiphon, Iraq; Palm Trees; Agriculture/Farms; Irrigation; Workers; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Tents; Horses; Animals; Cattle/Cows; Countryside/Rural; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Mosques; Streets/Roads; Religious Sites; Crowds; Markets; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Amarah (Al-'Amāra), Iraq; Uniforms; Guns; Weapons; Military/Soldiers; Navy; Air Force
- The back inside cover of the album 'Aviation in Mesopotamia Campaign WWI.', 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref27; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)
- The back cover of the album 'Aviation in Mesopotamia Campaign WWI.', 1916-1917; AD_MC_047_ref28; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_047)